A Guide to the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, Correspondence and subject files, 1998-2002
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Correspondence and subject files, 1998-2002
Library of Virginia
38946
18.7 cubic feet
Secretary of Commerce and Trade
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Office of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 11 January 2002.
Biographical/Historical Information
In 1970, the Governor's Management Commission Study recommended the creation of six "Deputy Governors" assist the Chief Executive in his managerial duties, compatible functions of government were grouped under these administrative heads, who would serve as the Governors top management team or "secretariats," as they are called now. The General Assembly in 1972 created six Secretariats positions initially. As government reorganized, that number fluctuated when government agencies expanded or consolidated.
The office of the Secretary of Commerce and Resources was established in 1972 and was responsible for the areas of economic development and natural resources. In 1986 this secretariat was dissolved and split into two separate offices, the Secretary of Economic Development and the Secretary of Natural Resources. In 1994 the name of the office was changed from the Secretary of Economic Development to the Secretary of Commerce and Trade.
The Secretary of Commerce and Trade is appointed by the governor and serves as a member of his cabinet. The Secretary of Commerce and Trade's chief responsibility is to manage the direction of several state agencies that are concerned with the development of commerce and economic development throughout the Commonwealth. Some of the agencies reporting to the Secretary of Commerce and Trade include: Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services; Department of Business Assistance; Virginia Economic Development Partnership; Department of Labor and Industry; Department of Mines, Minerals, and Energy; Virginia Employment Commission; Virginia Housing Development Authority; Department of Professional and Occupational Regulations; Department of Housing and Community Development; Milk Commission; Department of Minority Business Enterprise; Department of Forestry; Virginia Port Authority; Virginia Racing Commission; Virginia Resource Authority; and the Virginia Tourism Corporation.
Barry E. DuVal was appointed Virginia's Secretary of Commerce and Trade by Governor James S. Gilmore on January 5, 1998. Secretary DuVal graduated from James Madison University, and from 1983 until 1996 served as co-founder, president and principal broker of DuVal Associates, a diversified real estate firm. In 1988 he was elected to the City Council of Newport News and was elected Mayor in 1990, and was re- elected in 1992
Scope and Content Information
The records of Secretary of Commerce and Trade Barry E. DuVal consist of constituent correspondence and general correspondence and a subject files from the agencies under the administration of the secretary.
Series I: Constituent correspondence, 1998 Feb-2001 Dec. The constituent correspondence series contains letters and e-mail to the Governor's Office that were referred to the Secretary of Commerce and Trade for response, and some letters addressed directly to the office of the Secretary, on a variety of topics, including employment, housing issues, business opportunities, consumer complaints, animal rights, tobacco settlement, tourism and disaster relief. Files include original letters, referral slips containing customer contact information and tracking information, and copies of the response letters. Arranged by outgoing tracking/routing number.
Series II: Agency correspondence and subject files, 1998-2000. This series contains incoming and outgoing correspondence, reports, briefing binders, minutes, meeting and conference materials, publications and other records related to the agencies under the supervision of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, including the Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, Dept. of Business Administration, Dept. of Housing and Community Development, Virginia Housing Development Authority, Dept. of Labor and Industry, Milk Commission, Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of Minority Business Enterprises, Virginia Racing Commission, Virginia Resources Authority, Virginia Tourism Corporation, and the Virginia Economic Development Partnership (includes sub-series for Development Projects, Governor's Opportunity Fund, International Relations and Trade, Tourism Projects, University Programs and Virginia Film Office). Arranged alphabetically by agency.
Some of the records in this series predate the tenure of Secretary DuVal as far back as 1991 and additionally cover the administrations of Secretary of Economic Development Lawrence H. Framme, Secretary of Economic Development Cathleen A. Magennis, Secretary of Commerce and Trade Robert T. Skunda, and Secretary of Commerce and Trade Robert J. Stolle. These records apparently had been retained for continued use by the Office of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade.
Contents List
- Series I: Constituent correspondence, 1998 Feb-2001 Dec
  Arranged by outgoing tracking number.
  - Constituent correspondence #31-59, Feb 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Constituent correspondence #60-959, Feb-Mar 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Constituent correspondence #966-1583, Mar 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Constituent correspondence #1702-4585, Mar 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Constituent correspondence #5052-10980, Mar 1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Constituent correspondence #11070-11993, Mar 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Constituent correspondence #12010-15499, Mar-Apr 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Constituent correspondence #15664-17117, Apr 1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Constituent correspondence #17118-19464, Apr-May 1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Constituent correspondence #19578-20620, May 1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Constituent correspondence #20739-21167, May-Jun 1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Constituent correspondence #21354-22084, May-Jun 1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Constituent correspondence #22110-24366, Jun 1998 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Constituent correspondence #24381-25287, Jun 1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Constituent correspondence #25364-25833, Jun-Jul 1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Constituent correspondence #25853-26605, Jun-Jul 1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Constituent correspondence #26685-27132, Jun-Jul 1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Constituent correspondence #27135-27904, Jul 1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Constituent correspondence #28191-28522, Jul 1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Constituent correspondence #28524-28907, Jul 1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Constituent correspondence #28985-29741, Jul 1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Constituent correspondence #29778-30695, Aug 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Constituent correspondence #30721-31465, Aug-Sep 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Constituent correspondence #31466-31809, Sep 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Constituent correspondence #31863-32293, Sep 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Constituent correspondence #32325-32860, Sep 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Constituent correspondence #32865-33229, Sep 1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Constituent correspondence #33302-34598, Sep-Oct 1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Constituent correspondence #34606-35111, Oct 1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Constituent correspondence #35143-35554, Oct 1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Constituent correspondence #35648-35868, Oct 1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Constituent correspondence #35953-36203, Oct-Nov 1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Constituent correspondence #35215-36540, Nov 1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Constituent correspondence #36543-37457, Nov 1998 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Constituent correspondence #37558-37881, Nov-Dec 1998 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Constituent correspondence #37943-38237, Dec 1998 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Constituent correspondence #38242-38712, Dec 1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Constituent correspondence #48728-49111, Dec 1998 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Constituent correspondence #49155-49559, Dec 1998 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Constituent correspondence #49574-50038, Dec 1998-Jan 1999 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Constituent correspondence #50042-50319, Jan 1999 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Constituent correspondence #50349-50510, Jan 1999 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Constituent correspondence #50594-51437, Jan 1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Constituent correspondence #51476-52160, Jan 1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Constituent correspondence #52210-52696, Jan 1999 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Constituent correspondence #52697-53301, Jan 1999 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Constituent correspondence #53318-53492, Jan-Feb 1999 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Constituent correspondence #53518-54171, Feb 1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Constituent correspondence #54172-54631, Feb 1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Constituent correspondence #54886-55473, Feb 1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Constituent correspondence #55506-56169, Feb 1999 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Constituent correspondence #56250-57091, Feb-Mar 1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Constituent correspondence #57126-58185, Feb-Mar 1999 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Constituent correspondence #58309-60331, Mar 1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Constituent correspondence #60629-61538, Mar 1999 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Constituent correspondence #61625-62539, Mar-Apr 1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Constituent correspondence #62541-62956, Mar-Apr 1999 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Constituent correspondence #63055-63479, Apr 1999 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Constituent correspondence #63511-64639, Apr 1999 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Constituent correspondence #64717-65696, Apr 1999 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Constituent correspondence #65767-66539, Apr 1999 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Constituent correspondence #66827-67597, Apr-May 1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Constituent correspondence #67676-68379, Apr-May 1999 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Constituent correspondence #68429-68993, May 1999 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Constituent correspondence #69009-69980, May-Jun 1999 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Constituent correspondence #70016-70373, May-Jun 1999 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Constituent correspondence #70434-71283, May-Jun 1999 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Constituent correspondence #71350-72384, Jun 1999 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Constituent correspondence #72402-74196, Jun-Jul 1999 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Constituent correspondence #74230-75140, Jul 1999 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Constituent correspondence #75416-76867, Jul 1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Constituent correspondence #76917-77467, Jul 1999 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Constituent correspondence #77506-78098, Jul 1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Constituent correspondence #78110-78472, Jul 1999 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Constituent correspondence #78515-78943, Jul-Aug 1999 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Constituent correspondence #78973-79146, Aug 1999 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Constituent correspondence #79160-79768, Aug 1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Constituent correspondence #79804-79992, Aug 1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Constituent correspondence #80023-80398, Aug 1999 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Constituent correspondence #80408-80992, Aug 1999 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Constituent correspondence #81010-81234, Aug 1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Constituent correspondence #81253-81704, Aug-Sep 1999 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Constituent correspondence #81717-81988, Aug-Sep 1999 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Constituent correspondence #82010-82158, Aug-Sep 1999 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Constituent correspondence #82161-82324, Aug-Sep 1999 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Constituent correspondence #82336-82496, Aug 1999 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Constituent correspondence #82500-82740, Aug-Sep 1999 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Constituent correspondence #82761-83130, Sep 1999 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Constituent correspondence #83131-83359, Sep 1999 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Constituent correspondence #83386-83590, Sep 1999 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Constituent correspondence #83623-84272, Sep 1999 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Constituent correspondence #84394-84953, Sep 1999 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Constituent correspondence #85008-85356, Sep 1999 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Constituent correspondence #85422-85698, Sep 1999 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Constituent correspondence #85716-86700, Sep-Oct 1999 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Constituent correspondence #86705-87262, Sep-Oct 1999 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Constituent correspondence #87495-89371, Oct 1999 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Constituent correspondence #89381-89972, Oct 1999 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Constituent correspondence #90635-91774, Oct 1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Constituent correspondence #91001-91774, Oct-Nov 1999 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Constituent correspondence #91894-92451, Nov 1999 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Constituent correspondence #92521-93461, Nov 1999 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Constituent correspondence #93514-94048, Nov 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Constituent correspondence #94105-94821, Nov 1999 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Constituent correspondence #94830-95483, Nov 1999 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Constituent correspondence #95508-95787, Nov-Dec 1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Constituent correspondence #95797-96868, Dec 1999 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Constituent correspondence #96870-97192, Dec 1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Constituent correspondence #97214-97662, Dec 1999 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Constituent correspondence #97680-97921, Dec 1999 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Constituent correspondence #97954-98486, Dec 1999 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Constituent correspondence #98525-98859, Dec 1999-Jan 2000 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Constituent correspondence #98864-99167, Jan 2000 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Constituent correspondence #99177-99750, Jan 2000 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Constituent correspondence #99861-100455, Jan 2000 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Constituent correspondence #100627-101366, Jan-Feb 2000 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Constituent correspondence #100400-101989, Jan-Feb 2000 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Constituent correspondence #102021-102190, Feb 2000 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Constituent correspondence #102232-102507, Feb 2000 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Constituent correspondence #102549-102907, Feb 2000 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Constituent correspondence #103070-103965, Feb 2000 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Constituent correspondence #104193-104676, Feb 2000 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Constituent correspondence #104800-105183, Feb 2000 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Constituent correspondence #105260-105995, Feb-Mar 2000 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Constituent correspondence #106025-106459, Mar 2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Constituent correspondence #106525-107299, Mar 2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Constituent correspondence #107372-108425, Mar 2000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Constituent correspondence #108511-109295, Mar 2000 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Constituent correspondence #109335-110193, Mar 2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Constituent correspondence #110222-111286, Mar-Apr 2000 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Constituent correspondence #111486-112584, Apr 2000 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Constituent correspondence #112660-113976, Apr 2000 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Constituent correspondence #114319-114697, Apr 2000 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Constituent correspondence #115129-115766, Apr-May 2000 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Constituent correspondence #115901-116162, May 2000 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Constituent correspondence #200057-200297, May 2000 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Constituent correspondence #200300-200690, May 2000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Constituent correspondence #200721-200882, May 2000 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Constituent correspondence #200905-201399, May 2000 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Constituent correspondence #201420-202097, May 2000 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Constituent correspondence #202219-202360, May-Jun 2000 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Constituent correspondence #202407-202982, May-Jun 2000 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Constituent correspondence #203128-203699, May-Jun 2000 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Constituent correspondence #203700-203879, Jun 2000 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Constituent correspondence #203911-204290, Jun 2000 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Constituent correspondence #204302-204769, Jun 2000 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Constituent correspondence #204847-205382, Jun 2000 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Constituent correspondence #205413-205557, Jun-Jul 2000 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Constituent correspondence #205560-205839, Jun-Jul 2000 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Constituent correspondence #2003839; 2005426, Jun-Jul 2000 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Constituent correspondence #2006233-2006780, Jun-Jul 2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Constituent correspondence #2006818-2007347, Jul 2000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Constituent correspondence #2007418-2007978, Jul 2000 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Constituent correspondence #2008025-2008576, Jul 2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Constituent correspondence #2008629-2008991, Jul 2000 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Constituent correspondence #2009025-2009563, Jul-Aug 2000 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Constituent correspondence #2009623-2010390, Jul-Aug 2000 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Constituent correspondence #2010505-2010890, Aug 2000 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Constituent correspondence #2010962-2011560, Aug 2000 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Constituent correspondence #2011608-2012920, Aug 2000 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Constituent correspondence #2012115-2013993, Aug 2000 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Constituent correspondence #2014068-2014387, Sep 2000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Constituent correspondence #2014507-2016501, Sep 2000 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Constituent correspondence #2016613-2018681, Sep 2000 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Constituent correspondence #2019673-2025977, Sep-Oct 2000 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Constituent correspondence #2026063-2026590, Sep-Oct 2000 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Constituent correspondence #2026610-2026976, Oct 2000 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Constituent correspondence #2027038-2027927, Oct 2000 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Constituent correspondence #2028100-2028975, Oct 2000 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Constituent correspondence #2029023-2029994, Oct 2000 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Constituent correspondence #2030033-2030944, Oct 2000 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Constituent correspondence #2031032-2031986, Oct-Nov 2000 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Constituent correspondence #2032005-2032514, Nov 2000 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Constituent correspondence #2033053-2033582, Nov 2000 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Constituent correspondence #2033621-2034585, Nov 2000 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Constituent correspondence #2034600-2035144, Nov-Dec 2000 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Constituent correspondence #2035314-2035918, Dec 2000 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Constituent correspondence #2036029-2037118, Dec 2000 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Constituent correspondence #2037253-2037851, Dec 2000 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Constituent correspondence #2038266-2039295, Dec 2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Constituent correspondence #2039302-2039869, Dec 2000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Constituent correspondence #2040011-2040983, Jan 2001 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Constituent correspondence #2041003-2041996, Jan 2001 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Constituent correspondence #2042050-2042986, Jan 2001 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Constituent correspondence #2043618-2043867, Jan 2001 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Constituent correspondence #2044137-2044856, Jan 2001 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Constituent correspondence #2045018-2045817, Jan-Feb 2001 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Constituent correspondence #2046280-2046648, Feb 2001 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Constituent correspondence #2047491-2047991, Feb 2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Constituent correspondence #2048132-2048932, Feb 2001 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Constituent correspondence #2049075-2049327, Feb 2001 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Constituent correspondence #2050239-2050836, Feb 2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Constituent correspondence #2051061-2051991, Feb 2001 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Constituent correspondence #2052076-2052988, Feb 2001 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Constituent correspondence #2053304-2053753, Feb-Mar 2001 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Constituent correspondence #2054136-2054170, Feb-Mar 2001 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Constituent correspondence #2055098-2055989, Mar 2001 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Constituent correspondence #2056069-2056844, Mar 2001 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Constituent correspondence #2057097-2057989, Mar 2001 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Constituent correspondence #2058123-2058936, Mar 2001 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Constituent correspondence #2059081-2059998, Mar 2001 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Constituent correspondence #2060140-2060971, Mar-Apr 2001 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Constituent correspondence #2061015-2061711, Apr 2001 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Constituent correspondence #2062185-2062357, Apr 2001 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Constituent correspondence #2062452-2062961, Apr 2001 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Constituent correspondence #2063060-2063398, Apr 2001 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Constituent correspondence #2063430-2063990, Apr 2001 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Constituent correspondence #2064035-2064885, Apr 2001 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Constituent correspondence #2065076-2065994, Apr 2001 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Constituent correspondence #2066025-2066861, Apr-May 2001 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Constituent correspondence #2067139-2067596, May 2001 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Constituent correspondence #2067646-2067916, May 2001 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Constituent correspondence #2068021-2068449, May 2001 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Constituent correspondence #2068509-2068983, May 2001 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Constituent correspondence #2069079-2069910, May 2001 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Constituent correspondence #2070001-2070497, Jun 2001 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Constituent correspondence #2070576-2070981, Jun 2001 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Constituent correspondence #2071017-2071599, Jun 2001 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Constituent correspondence #2071650-2071867, Jun 2001 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Constituent correspondence #2072015-2072637, Jun 2001 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Constituent correspondence #2072648-2072976, Jun 2001 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Constituent correspondence #2073025-2073371, Jun 2001 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Constituent correspondence #2073394-2073967, Jun-Jul 2001 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Constituent correspondence #2074014-2074969, Jul 2001 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Constituent correspondence #2075028-2075491, Jul 2001 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Constituent correspondence #2075546-2075913, Jul-Aug 2001 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Constituent correspondence #2076596-2076929, Aug 2001 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Constituent correspondence #2077008-2077788, Aug 2001 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Constituent correspondence #2077861-2077996, Aug 2001 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Constituent correspondence #2078053-2078581, Aug 2001 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Constituent correspondence #2078632-2078986, Aug 2001 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Constituent correspondence #2079004-2079423, Aug 2001 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Constituent correspondence #2079551-2079980, Aug-Sep 2001 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Constituent correspondence #2080015-2080472, Sep 2001 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Constituent correspondence #2080508-2080913, Sep 2001 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Constituent correspondence #2081019-2081488, Sep 2001 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Constituent correspondence #2081518-2081901, Sep-Oct 2001 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Constituent correspondence #2082092-2082585, Sep-Oct 2001 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Constituent correspondence #2082614-2082964, Oct 2001 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Constituent correspondence #2083005-2083586, Oct 2001 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Constituent correspondence #2083619-2083998, Oct 2001 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Constituent correspondence #2084001-2084299, Oct 2001 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Constituent correspondence #2084336-2084599, Oct 2001 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Constituent correspondence #2084602-2084869, Oct 2001 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Constituent correspondence #2085206-2085358, Oct-Nov 2001 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Constituent correspondence #2085412-2085698, Nov 2001 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Constituent correspondence #2085700-2085964, Nov 2001 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Constituent correspondence #2086071-2086484, Nov 2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)